ABDUL MOID KHAN MOHAMMED

-- CSE UNDERGRADUATE --

Current College MCET Abids , (OU) Address: Baitul AR ,Rajendranagar,

Email amkhan357@gmail.com Attapur , 500030

Website khanisic.github.io/Portfolio **Phone:** +91 - 6309535275

ABOUT

I am an undergraduate student, pursuing Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science. I seek to take on domineering and demeaning challenges in life so I can push past the barriers and experience the phenomenal. I'm driven towards my goals and my main goal is to become the best version of myself..

Some of my qualities are **Leadership**, **Efficient Work Ethic**, **Hardworking** and **Time Management**

EDUCATION

2005 - 2018 International Indian School Dammam

KG-12th

Methodist College of Engineering and Technology

2018 - PRESENT CSE - 3rd Year

EXPERIENCE

GLOBAL PRIDE INTL SCHOOL

Web Developer

苗 July 2020 - September 2020

Designed and Developed a website for the company.

gpis.in

WOMEN'S ASSOCIATION FORUM - CHICAGO

Web Developer

i August 2020 - October 2020

 Designed and Developed a website for the company.

wafchicago.org

METTECH MEDIA

Web Developer & Co - Founder

May 2020 - present

- Designed and Developed a website for the company.
- Manage Clientele
- Build wireframes and UI

mettech.in

SKILLS

• Languages : javaScript | C++ | Python | SQL

• Databases : MongoDB

• **Frameworks :** Django | React.js | Bootstrap

• Tools Node.js

PERSONAL SKILLS

HOBBIES

Team Management | Listening to podcast | Teamwork | Ability to work under pressure | Quick Learner Football | Running | Basketball | Gaming | Trading

HACKATHONS AND PROJECTS

Hackathons: -

- NASA Space Apps Challenge Regional Winner Built a Time Capsule using Blender 3d and Research.
- SRM Hackathon
 Designed a street patrolling camera for safety

Projects so far:-

- Built a Grievance Redressal Portal as a mini project at college using Django
- Built a Netflix Clone using REACT.JS
- Built an Instagram Clone using MERN Stack